{
    "subject": "Marty_Feldman",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "In_God_We_Tru$t",
    "human_readable": "Marty Feldman directed the film In God We Tru$t.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9347386360168457,
            "question": "Who directed the film In God We Tru$t?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8378246426582336,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Marty Feldman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7069196105003357,
            "question": "What year was the film In God We Tru$t released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6792357563972473,
            "question": "Were there any notable actors in the film In God We Tru$t?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6162797808647156,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in a film titled In God We Tru$t?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6157777905464172,
            "question": "Can you name other films directed by Marty Feldman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6113598942756653,
            "question": "How was the film In God We Tru$t received by critics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5458667874336243,
            "question": "What genre might the film In God We Tru$t belong to based on its title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4349242150783539,
            "question": "Would you recommend watching In God We Tru$t?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31994929909706116,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the title and Marty Feldman's comedic style?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marty Feldman directed the film In God We Tru$t.",
            "html": "yago_27938_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you recommend watching In God We Tru$t?",
            "html": "yago_27938_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the film In God We Tru$t belong to based on its title?",
            "html": "yago_27938_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was the film In God We Tru$t received by critics?",
            "html": "yago_27938_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27938_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents contain several references to Marty Feldman's directing work, including his co-writing and directing of the film \"In God We Tru$t\", as mentioned in files `21.txt`, `23.txt`, `29.txt`. This supports the triple statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Marty Feldman directed the film In God We Trust.\" Both `11.txt`, `29.txt`, and `23.txt` explicitly mention that the film was co-written, directed, and starring Marty Feldman."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}